I thought I'd let you know where I'm
going to be speaking publicly now until
the end of 2018 I've been touring for
about three months discussing the issues
of meaning and responsibility raised in
my books twelve rules for life and maps
of meaning here are the Canadian
American and European cities I will be
traveling to over the next five months
Cincinnati Tuesday September 18th
Cleveland
Wednesday September 19th Grand Rapids
Thursday September 20th des Moines
Tuesday October 2nd st. Louis Wednesday
October 3rd Kansas City Thursday October
4th Denver Sunday October 7th Colorado
Springs Monday October 8th San Antonio
Wednesday October 10th
Irving Thursday October 11th Honolulu
Wednesday November 21st Los Angeles
Saturday December 1st back in Canada
Calgary Thursday December 4th Vancouver
Wednesday December 5th then it's off to
Europe
Dublin Sunday October 21st Oslo Tuesday
October 23rd Manchester Thursday October
25th Oxford Friday October 26th Glasgow
Saturday October 27th Edinburgh Sunday
October 28th Amsterdam Tuesday October
30th Cambridge Thursday November 1st
Helsinki Sunday November 4th Stockholm
Monday November 5th and Birmingham
Wednesday November 7th we'll be adding
some more cities to the European leg of
this tour
they'll be announced soon and also we're
going to Australia in February and then
back to Europe in April of 2019 those
dates will be announced in the
relatively near future it's been really
something to tour around like this and
these events have been extremely
positive so if you're inclined to come
out and hear me lecture you'd be more
than welcome thank you very much
bye-bye